{
    "id": "d7354de4493848e5b13b3f2c53757fd4",
    "title": "Articles With Uncountable And Countable Nouns",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We are having .......................... weather.",
            "description": "Weather is an uncountable noun. We cannot use the articles a/an with it. ",
            "answers": [
                "awful",
                "an awful",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1e937dffe2f9428fbe9652d09098a318"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you got ............................ for dry skin?",
            "description": "Sometimes uncountable nouns are treated as countable to express the meaning 'a type of'.",
            "answers": [
                "cold cream",
                "a cold cream",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5fca1e38095a4b87902e00348b13d0ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have made ............................. progress.",
            "description": "Progress is an uncountable noun and it cannot be used with the article a.",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0d69f21c2a2e47b195fcaa5390a805ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "The applicant should be able to speak ..................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a good English",
                "good English",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "07328df75bf24c94b0d05f852dab5995"
        },
        {
            "question": "We haven't seen ......................... in days.",
            "description": "We use the article 'the' to talk about something unique. ",
            "answers": [
                "sun",
                "the sun",
                "a sun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "639dbba7838741818e8d2660ecc18294"
        },
        {
            "question": "How did ....................... first discover fire?",
            "description": "The noun 'man' is commonly used to mean 'the human race'. No articles are used in this case. ",
            "answers": [
                "man",
                "the man",
                "a man"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c22a4c1930644519bf1fad0f893772b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... have their own language and culture.",
            "description": "The Irish means all people belonging to Ireland. ",
            "answers": [
                "Irish",
                "The Irish",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f39d1bb19d904ce7ac51f8bdd843544a"
        },
        {
            "question": "My children like ............................. but I prefer ...........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the sea, mountains",
                "sea, mountains",
                "the sea, the mountains"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "27c99bc2c02a4516978f247cc0ac383e"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................ are losing hope.",
            "description": "The unemployed means all unemployed people. ",
            "answers": [
                "Unemployed",
                "The unemployed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d38ff638f60e4700aa64e58c564d4d5e"
        },
        {
            "question": "This engine does not use ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "petrol",
                "the petrol",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e484726f988b44a0811807a8acd20b95"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................... is quite complicated.",
            "description": "No article is used when we talk about the whole of life. ",
            "answers": [
                "Life",
                "The life",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e061c4d8a3ae4b77a17c7800bc3dfa1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am studying ........................ of Lincoln.",
            "description": "We use the article 'the' here because we are talking about one particular life. ",
            "answers": [
                "life",
                "the life",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "be78034969ff497186b3064a7360357f"
        }
    ]
}